Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 14, Folder: 129, Publication (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Item 1: How Our Business System Operates, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 129)
- Box: 14, Folder: 130, Publication (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 130)
- Box: 15, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Preparing For Negotiations, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Box: 15, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The New Economic Forces At The Bargaining Table, 1971; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Box: 15, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Facts About The Strike Against General Electric, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Box: 15, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Letter To Sales and Service People On The Outlook For 1966 Negotiations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Box: 15, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: News: Special Edition October 1969, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Box: 15, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: News: Supplement September 1969, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Box: 15, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1961; Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Box: 15, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X5, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Box: 15, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X6, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Box: 15, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X7, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Box: 15, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X8, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Box: 15, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X9, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Box: 15, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X10, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Box: 15, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X11, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Box: 15, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X12, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Box: 15, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X13, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Box: 15, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 69-35X14, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Box: 15, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-X, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Box: 15, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-X2, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Box: 15, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-X3, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Box: 15, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-X4, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Box: 15, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-X5, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Box: 15, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-X6, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Box: 15, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-X7, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Box: 15, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-1, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Box: 15, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-2, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Box: 15, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-4, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Box: 15, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Relations Reviews No. 70-5, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Box: 15, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Union Negotiations, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Box: 15, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Labor Management Relations In a Newly Competitive World, 1965; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Box: 15, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Service With The Federal Government, 1964; Publication (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Box: 15, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Labor Management Relations, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Box: 15, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Management, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Box: 15, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Box: 15, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Box: 15, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The Quest For Leadership and Excellence, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Box: 15, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1965; Publication (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Box: 15, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Competition, 1964; Publication (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Box: 15, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Workman's Compensation, 1961; Publication (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Box: 15, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Appraisal and Personnel Development, 1963; Publication (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Box: 15, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Labor Policy, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Box: 15, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: The Search For Leadership, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 42)
    Author: Richard J. Anton
- Box: 15, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Management Reports, 1963; Publication (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Box: 15, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Wage Stabilization and Inflation, 1951; Publication (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Box: 15, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Toward A Sense of Managerial Purpose, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Box: 15, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Management Education, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Box: 15, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Efficient Organizational Structure, 1953; Publication (Box 15, Folder 47)
    Author: Ralph J. Cordiner
- Box: 15, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Health Insurance, 1961; Publication (Box 15, Folder 48)
    Author: Charles E. Tosch
- Box: 15, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits, 1961; Publication (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Box: 15, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Our Larger Job In 1957, Publication (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Box: 15, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1956; Publication (Box 15, Folder 51)
    Author: Harold Smiddy
- Box: 15, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Management Labor Problem For 1955, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Box: 15, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: How Far To Harmonious Relationship, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Box: 15, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Information Program For Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Box: 15, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: The Right To Work, 1953; Publication (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Box: 15, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Community Relations Responsibility, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Box: 15, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1962; Publication (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Box: 15, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Which Way America, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Box: 15, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Box: 15, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 15, Folder 60)
    Author: E.J. Kneeland
- Box: 15, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations, 1962; Publication (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Box: 15, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Human Resource Development, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Box: 15, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Policies, 1955; Publication (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Box: 15, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: The Monogram, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Box: 15, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Personnel Administration Code, 1955; Publication (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Box: 15, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Benefit Program, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Box: 15, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Economic Program, 1964; Publication (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Box: 15, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Program For Security, 1959; Publication (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Box: 15, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Job Talk, 1959; Publication (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Box: 15, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Key Personnel Development, 1958; Publication (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Box: 15, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: College Relations, 1959; Publication (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Box: 15, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Selection Research Reports, 1955; Publication (Box 15, Folder 72)
- Box: 16, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan and Policy, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Box: 16, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Training Review, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Box: 16, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Solving Problems By Practicing Consultative Supervision, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Box: 16, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Training Experience Review, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Box: 16, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan For Hourly Rated Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Box: 16, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan For Salaried Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Box: 16, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: How The American Economic System Operates, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Box: 16, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan For Salaried Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Box: 16, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Non-Occupational Accident and Sickness Disability Plan For Hourly Employees, 1958; Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Box: 16, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Non-Occupational Accident and Sickness Disability Plan For Salaried Employees, 1958; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Box: 16, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan For Hourly Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Box: 16, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Non-Occupational Accident and Sickness Disability Benefit Plan For Hourly Rated Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Box: 16, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Introducing The New Employee To His Company and His Job, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Box: 16, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A Guide To Industrial Feeding In The Company Cafeteria, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Box: 16, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Preparing For Negotiations, 1954; Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Box: 16, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Program For Security, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Box: 16, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: How Are You Doing On Your Job?, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Box: 16, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Bulletin Boards, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Box: 16, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Training Methods, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Box: 16, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Making Your Meetings Pay Off, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Box: 16, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Employment Procedure, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Box: 16, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Discrimination In Employment, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Box: 16, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Box: 16, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Tips On Interview, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Box: 16, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Sales Management, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Box: 16, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Introduction of New Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Box: 16, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Box: 16, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Box: 16, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: New York Times Article- January 13, 1951, Publication (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Box: 16, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Managerial Position Evaluation, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Box: 16, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relation Survey, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Box: 16, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Identification Card, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Box: 16, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Program For Security, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Box: 16, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Our Company, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Box: 16, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Organization and Products, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Box: 16, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Basic Flour Mills, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Box: 16, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Maintenance Training Program, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Box: 16, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Box: 16, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Personal Administration Department, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Box: 16, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Revision Of Industrial Relations Department Memorandum No. 23, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Box: 16, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1970; Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Box: 16, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Agreement, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Box: 16, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Management Development Concepts and Principles, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Box: 16, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1970; Publication (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Box: 16, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: You and The Master Agreement, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Box: 16, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: History of General Mills, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Box: 16, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Employment Tests, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Box: 16, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: College Recruiting Procedures, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Box: 16, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Application for Employment, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Box: 16, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Application For Membership, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Box: 16, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Personnel Inventory, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Box: 16, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Management and Manpower Building, 1956; Publication (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Box: 16, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Box: 16, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Retirement and Death Benefit Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Box: 16, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Multiple Group Retirement Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Box: 16, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Maintaining A Strong Domestic Economy, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Box: 16, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Box: 16, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: The Halm and Welfare Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Box: 16, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: My Company, 1973; Publication (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Box: 16, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Box: 16, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: How You Can Get Ideas and Make Them Pay Off, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Box: 16, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: A Look At The Company and The Job, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Box: 16, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Box: 16, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: College Recruiting, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 64)
- Box: 16, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Box: 16, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: You and Your Job, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Box: 16, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Compensation, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Box: 16, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Health Association, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Box: 16, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Compensation, 1954; Publication (Box 16, Folder 69)
- Box: 16, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 70)
- Box: 16, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Health and Welfare Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 16, Folder 71)
- Box: 16, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1956; Publication (Box 16, Folder 72)
- Box: 16, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Cash For Your Ideas, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Box: 16, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Major Medical and Life Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 16, Folder 74)
- Box: 16, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Yesterday and Today, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 75)
- Box: 16, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Employee Retirement System, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 76)
- Box: 16, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Health Association, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 77)
- Box: 16, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Health Benefits, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 78)
- Box: 16, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Basic Policies, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 79)
- Box: 16, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Sketches From The General Mills Story, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 80)
- Box: 16, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Multiple Group Retirement Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 16, Folder 81)
- Box: 16, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 16, Folder 82)
- Box: 16, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Education Advancement, 1963; Publication (Box 16, Folder 83)
- Box: 16, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention Program, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 84)
- Box: 16, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Rating Employees, 1960; Publication (Box 16, Folder 85)
- Box: 16, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement System, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 86)
- Box: 17, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Minimum Standards For Safe Plan Operations, 1952; Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Box: 17, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Mature Collective Bargaining Prospects and Problems, 1951; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Box: 17, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Newspaper Article, 1951; Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Box: 17, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 1951 Car Prices and The Price 'Roll-Back', Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Box: 17, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Plant Protection and Fire Prevention, 1951; Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Box: 17, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Philosophy Behind Contract Settlement, 1951; Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Box: 17, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Five Years of Industrial Peace, 1950; Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Box: 17, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary, 1973; Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Box: 17, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 1967-1968 Engineering Program Catalogue, Publication (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Box: 17, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Public Relations, 1964; Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Box: 17, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Quit Report, 1952; Publication (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Box: 17, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Agreement, 1950; Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Box: 17, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Year In Review, 1972; Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Box: 17, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Comments On Five Year Contract, 1950; Publication (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Box: 17, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: President's Reply, 1957; Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Box: 17, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Letter From The President, 1958; Publication (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Box: 17, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Progress, Productivity, Wages, 1951; Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Author: C.E. Wilson
- Box: 17, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 17, Folder 18)